theautoinsurancescout.com 2011-12-30

# The Auto Insurance Scout - Privacy Policy

NOTICE: Privacy Policy Effective April 15, 2011  
The The Auto Insurance Scout Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting The Auto Insurance Scout website located at www.TheAutoInsuranceScout.com (the "Site"). The Site is an Internet property of Targeted Solutions Online and its affiliated companies ("Targeted Solutions Online," "we" or "us"). This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") outlines the privacy practices associated with the Site. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (a) access or use the Site; (b) agree to receive e-mail from us via the Site, or any other means; (c) register on the Site to receive auto-insurance-related products and/or services ("insurance services") from our third party service providers ("Third Party Service Providers"); and/or (d) obtain, or attempt to obtain, any Targeted Solutions Online products and/or services.

For purposes of compliance with the California Financial Privacy Act and the Vermont Consumer Protection Act, 8 V.S.A. 10202, if you are a resident of the State of California or Vermont and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third-party for marketing purposes, please Click Here. Please be advised that where California or Vermont residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with the law. 

When you register on our Site, you hereby agree and acknowledge that your personal information will be placed into the Targeted Solutions Online database and that such personal information shall be shared with third parties for marketing purposes. 

## Your IP Address 

Each time that you visit the Site, our web server automatically recognizes your IP address and the web page from which you came. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you. We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, to administer the Site and to better serve you in using the products, services and other features contained within the Site. 

Cookies and Action Tags 

**Cookies:** The first time that a user provides an e-mail address in connection with their activities at the Site, we assign an identification number to that e-mail address and deploy a cookie to the applicable user’s PC. Whenever that user comes back to the Site using the same PC, the cookie allows the Site to identify the user and to recall the ’s e-mail address. If, at any time, a user provides other information in connection with their activities on the Site (such as name, address, birth date, gender, etc.), we may store that information, along with the user’s e-mail address, in our user database. We may use the information stored in our database: (a) to effectuate the purpose or transaction for which the information was originally provided by a user; (b) to pre-populate information fields in the event that user wishes to purchase products and/or services or sign up for and/or subscribe to services, promotions or other offers in the future; (c) to ensure that a user will not be repeatedly exposed to the same advertisements, offers and/or promotions while visiting the Site; and/or (d) to, in connection with regular communication with a user, include offers, promotions or advertisements that were historically, or are likely to be, of interest to that user. We also use cookies to anonymously track and target the interests of our users to further enhance the experience on the Site. To find out more about cookies, please visit [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/). To disable and reject cookies, adjust the settings via the toolbar options menu of your internet browser. 

**Action Tags, Web Beacons and other Data Collection Methods:** An action tag or a web-beacon (also known as a clear gif or a pixel tag) is a method used to track responses or actions by visitors who view certain advertisements or other information on the Site. Action tags are 1x1 pixel images embedded in a website page that are used to transparently collect information. We may use action tags to count the number of times that visitors click on a particular banner ad or visit the pages of the Site and to provide information about what products/services are viewed or purchased. We reserve the right to retain this cookie and action tag data indefinitely, and to share information generated by these cookies and action tags with our advertisers, affiliates and service providers.

## Personal Information We Collect from You 

We collect your personally identifiable information when you sign up to receive insurance services at the Site. We may also collect your personally identifiable information when you otherwise agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, but do not complete the applicable registration process in full. The types of personally identifiable information that we collect at the Site and/or when you sign up to receive insurance services include, without limitation: (a) your e-mail address; (b) state of residence; and/or (c) any other information requested on the applicable application. 

## How We Use Personal Information 

By submitting your personal information on the Site, you agree that we may share such personal information with our Third Party Service Providers in order to complete your request for insurance services. Our Third Party Service Providers may use such personal information for any lawful purposes, subject to any restrictions contained herein including, without limitation, in connection with contacting you for purposes of completing your application for the insurance services. Any information that you subsequently supply to any Third Party Service Providers shall be governed by such Third Party Service Providers’ privacy policies. Please be advised that Targeted Solutions Online does not itself provide auto-insurance-related products and/or services. The insurance services will be provided by Third Party Service Providers, and the ultimate terms and conditions of the insurance services will be determined by those Third Party Service Providers. 

We may share the personal information that you supply to us with any third party and we may work with other businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our users. These businesses and third parties may include, but are not limited to: (a) providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation; (b) e-mail marketers; (c) telemarketers; (d) SMS text-based marketers (where permitted by applicable law); and (e) direct marketers. 

We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from user lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. The agents performing these limited functions on our behalf shall have access to our users’ personal information as needed to perform their functions for us but we do not permit them to use your personal information for other purposes. 

Additionally, we purchase and manage e-mail lists generated by third parties. Users may remove themselves from a specific mailing list by utilizing the unsubscribe options that are present and available at the end of each piece of e-mail that we send. 

We will also use your personal information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may request, to customize your experience on the Site and/or to contact you when necessary in connection with transactions entered into by you on the Site. We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our business. We may also combine the information we have gathered about you with information from other sources. We may use third parties to help us operate our business and the Site or to administer activities on our behalf. 

We also reserve the right to release current or past user information in the event that we believe that the user is using, or has used, our products, services and/or Site: (i) in violation of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy or any other of our operating rules, policies, price schedules and other supplemental terms and conditions or documents that may be published by us from time to time; (ii) to commit unlawful acts; (iii) if such information is subpoenaed; (iv) if we are sold or acquired; and/or (v) when we deem it necessary or appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, and Federal Trade Commission implementing regulations. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, we reserve the right to share, sell, rent, lease and/or otherwise distribute any and all personal information with/to any third party for any and all uses permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law. 

By registering at the Site, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR §310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the "Rule") and applicable state do-not-call regulations. As such, notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, and/or on applicable state do-not-call lists, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the Rule and the applicable state do-not-call regulations. 

In addition, you agree that by submitting your personal information at the Site, you agree to receive mobile marketing including, but not limited to, text-message based marketing, from us and our third party advertisers and marketers (where, and to the extent that, such marketing is permitted by applicable law). As such, notwithstanding that your mobile telephone number may be listed on state and/or federal Do-Not-Call registries, we retain the right to contact you via text-message based marketing in accordance with applicable state and federal law. Further, you agree that we reserve the right to share, sell, rent, lease and/or otherwise distribute your mobile telephone and other mobile data with/to any third-party for any and all non-marketing uses permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law. 

You may unsubscribe from any of our e-mail marketing programs at any time. In every e-mail communication that we send, there is an unsubscribe hyperlink that allows the recipient to unsubscribe from the specific marketing program by simply clicking the hyperlink provided and following the instructions that follow. We attempt to process all unsubscribe requests in a prompt fashion. However, after unsubscribing, we cannot guarantee that you will never receive another mailing from us, because we may obtain your e-mail address in the future through a different e-mail marketing program that you have opted into. We can guarantee, however, that if you should ever receive another e-mail communication from us, you will be able to remove your e-mail address via the unsubscribe hyperlink. We are able to offer our free services, in part, based upon the willingness of our users to be contacted by our marketing partners, including affiliated third party advertisers. By allowing us to make the information that you supply available to our marketing partners, you will receive free product and service information that may be of interest to you. You may, at any time, notify us that you do not wish to have your personal information disclosed to third parties for offers and promotions by sending an e-mail to [info@targetedsolutionsonline.com](mailto:info@targetedsolutionsonline.com)[](mailto:unsubscribe@customerpermissionservices.com). 

**How We Use Demographic Information and Aggregate Data**

We use demographic information to tailor the Site to the interests of our users. Demographic information is shared with third party advertisers so that they can tailor their advertisements to the appropriate audience. Demographic information may also be shared with other third parties. 

We reserve the right to provide aggregate or group data about our users for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage or characteristics of our participants as a group, without disclosing personally identifiable information. By opening an account with us, you agree to allow us to provide such aggregate data to third parties. By agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you hereby consent to the disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be appropriate. 

## Other Websites 

This Site may contain links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites including, but not limited to, the websites of our Third Party Service Providers. Targeted Solutions Online is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be able to make a purchase through one of their third-party websites. In these instances, you may be required to provide certain information, such as a credit card number, to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and Targeted Solutions Online has no responsibility or liability relating to them.

## Third-Party Offers 

Targeted Solutions Online provides its users with the opportunity to receive special offers, products and/or services from third parties including, but not limited to, our Third Party Service Providers. Where you indicate the desire to receive certain offers, products or services from a third party during the applicable information collection process, your personally identifiable information that was provided during that Targeted Solutions Online information collection process will be shared with the applicable third party so that such third party may provide their product or service to you and so that you do not have to complete another information collection form (or re-supply the same information) to purchase or receive that product or service.

## Our Security Precautions

We endeavor to safeguard and protect our users’ information. When users submit information at the Site, their information is protected both online and off-line. The privacy of your personal information is very important to us. The servers that we store personally identifiable information in are kept in a secure physical environment. We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. Please be advised that, although we take every reasonable technological precaution available to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through our Site is at your own risk. However, access to your information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. All of our users’ information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personal information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user information. Employees not adhering to our firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your Personal Information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures. 

## Minors

No information should be submitted to, or posted at, the Site by visitors under eighteen (18) years of age. Persons eighteen (18) years of age and younger are not permitted to access the Site and we do not knowingly collect personal information from such individuals. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

## Removal of Your Information/Opting Out

At your request, we will remove personal information that you have provided to us. You may do so by e-mailing us at [info@targetedsolutionsonline.com](mailto:info@targetedsolutionsonline.com)[](mailto:unsubscribe@customerpermissionservices.com). However, deleting your Personal Information, or otherwise opting-out of receipt of communications from us or third parties, will only change or delete the data in our database for purposes of transacting future business on the Site and for managing future communications from us and third parties. These deletions will not change or delete personal information already collected as part of a particular transaction in our database, which may have already been shared with third parties, all as provided above in this Privacy Policy. You will need to contact third parties who may contact you directly to change your preferences or your personal information that they may be using to contact you.

We provide users with the option to opt-out from receiving information sent via electronic mailings on behalf of third party advertisers. Users may unsubscribe from receiving e-mails at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every e-mailing. Unsubscribe requests can only be processed if you have registered with us in the first instance. If you have not registered with us and wish to opt out of receiving e-mails from a particular sender, please consult that sender’s opt out policies or contact that sender.

Information sent on behalf of third party advertisers is prepared several days in advance, so users may continue to receive e-mail from us for up to ten (10) days following the unsubscribe procedures detailed above. If, after that point, a user is still receiving e-mail from us, the user should contact us at [info@targetedsolutionsonline.com](mailto:info@targetedsolutionsonline.com)[](mailto:legal@customerpermissionservices.com).

## No Liability for Unauthorized Changes

IN NO EVENT SHALL WE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF THE SITE OR FOR THE UNAUTHORIZED MODIFICATION OF TEXT OR ADVERTISEMENTS PROVIDED BY US, OUR MARKETING PARTNERS OR ANY OTHER THIRD PARTIES.

## Your Acceptance of these Terms

By using this Site including, without limitation, signing up for offers and/or continuing to receive information from us, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site or acceptance of our e-mails following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept these changes and agree to continue receiving e-mails from us. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please unsubscribe by Clicking Here.

## Contacting Us about Privacy Questions or Concerns 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Site or your dealings with the Site, please e-mail us at [info@targetedsolutionsonline.com](mailto:info@targetedsolutionsonline.com), or send a letter to: Targeted Solutions Online, 1000 N. West Street, Suite 1200, Wilmington, DE 19801,  **or call us at (954) 423-0260**
